Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Writings and Speeches, 1912-2000 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Open Files, 1912-1993 and undated
  - Johnson, Arno (continued), (65-73 of 112 folders) (Box 22)
    - 1958. 32.6. Client talk. Oneida Ltd. Talk at sales meeting (Box 22)
    - 1958. 32.7. Speech. America's Economy Today (Box 22)
    - 1959. 32.8. Client talk. Pan American World Airlines. Potential in European Travel Is Tenfold Greater Than Actually Realized (Box 22)
    - 1959. 32.9. New Business. Kingsberry Homes (Lumber Fabricators, Inc.). Some Factors That May Influence the Market for Summer Homes (Box 22)
    - 1959. 32.10. Speech. Setting Our Sights for the '60's (Box 22)
    - 1959. 32.11. Speech. Your Marketing Opportunities 1959-60 (Box 22)
    - 1959. 32.12. Other writing. Glassware trends: three charts (table) (Box 22)
    - 1959. 32.13. Speech. Food Market Can Expand Sixty Per Cent Next Ten Years (Box 22)
    - 1959. 32.14. New Business. National Lead Company. Meeting. (Box 22)
    - 1959. 32.15. Article. World Trade Boom Ahead with Rapid Advances in Living Standards. Advertising Age, Market Data issue, Apr. 20 (Box 22)
    - 1959. 33.1. Speech. Your Sales Future--Opportunity for Increased Consumption of Eggs & Poultry Through Increased Promotion (Box 22)
    - 1959. 33.2. Speech. Economic Guideposts for Milk-Merchandising (Box 22)
    - 1959. 33.3. Speech. Future Opportunities for the Dairy Industry (Box 22)
    - 1959. 33.4. Speech. Trading Areas--Becoming Obsolete (Box 22)
    - 1959. 33.5. Speech. How Advertising Stimulates Improvement of Living Standards & Expansion of Trade (Box 22)
  - Johnson, Arno (continued), (74-80 of 112 folders) (Box 23)
    - 1959. 33.6. Letter. To: S. W. Meek, re: Growth in Red Cross Endowment Fund (Box 23)
    - 1959. 33.7. Speech. Marketing Tomorrow (Box 23)
    - 1959. 33.8. Speech. Current Economic Outlook (Box 23)
    - 1959. 33.9. Speech. World Trade Boom Ahead with Rapid Advances in Living Standards in Western Europe and U.S. (Box 23)
    - 1959. 33.10. Speech. Setting Our Sights for the Sixties (Box 23)
    - 1959. 33.11. Speech. Setting Our Sights for the Sixties (Box 23)
    - 1959. 33.12. Client talk. Lever Brothers. Trends in the U.S. Economy (Box 23)
    - 1959. 34.1. Speech. Marketing Today and Tomorrow (Box 23)
    - 1959. 34.2. Speech. Economic Guideposts for Milk Merchandising (Box 23)
    - 1959. 34.3. Speech. Setting Our Sights for the Sixties (Box 23)
    - 1959. 34.4. Speech. Setting Our Sights for the Sixties (Box 23)
    - 1959. 34.5. Speech. Setting Our Sights for the Sixties (Box 23)
    - 1959. 34.6. Speech. Advertising in the Sixties (Box 23)
    - 1959. 34.7. Article. Decade of Retail Expansion 1960-1970. Profit Parade section, Haire Publications, Dec. (Box 23)
    - 1959. 34.8. Letter. To: NAS-NRC Conference Committee on Beef, re: Beef for Tomorrow (Box 23)
    - 1959. 34.9. Article. $115 Billion Consumer Food Potential by 1970--Up 60%. Food Topics, Jan. (Box 23)
    - 1959. 34.10. Client talk. Owens Illinois Management Meeting. Let's Set Our Sights Toward '70 (Box 23)
    - 1959. 34.11. Client talk. Kraft. Four charts used at meeting (Box 23)
    - 1959. 34.12. Article. House & Home. Round table report on tight money (Box 23)
    - 1960. 35.1. Speech. Setting Our Sights for the ‘60s (Box 23)
    - 1960. 35.2. Client talk. Oscar Mayer. Setting Our Sights for the ‘60s (Box 23)
    - 1960. 35.3. Speech. Setting Our Sights for the ‘60s (Box 23)
    - 1960. 35.4. Client talk. Rice Industry. Food in the Sixties: Opportunity for Expansion of Rice Consumption (Box 23)
    - 1960. 35.5. Client talk. United States Brewers Foundation. Setting Our Sights for the Sixties (Box 23)
    - 1960. 35.6. Speech. From Habit-Lag to Habit-Leap in the Magic Sixties (Box 23)
    - 1960. 35.7. Speech. Setting Our Sights for the Sixties (Box 23)
    - 1960. 35.7a. Client talk. McGraw-Edison Company. Setting Our Sights for the Sixties (Box 23)
    - 1960. 35.7b. Client talk. New Holland. Setting Our Sights for the ‘60s (Box 23)
    - 1960. 35.8. Speech. Marketing Opportunities during the Next Decade (Box 23)
    - 1960. 35.9. Letter. To: George Dibert, re: New business--wheat promotion (Box 23)
    - 1960. 35.9a. Letter. To: Harry A. Lee, re: Statement by the Hon. Maxwell Stamp on dollar crisis (Box 23)
    - 1960. 35.10. Article. 1960 Slowdown Can Be Reversed by 1961. Advertising Age, Market Data issue, Apr. 18 (Box 23)
    - 1960. 35.10a. Speech. Setting Our Sights for the ‘60s (Box 23)
    - 1960. 35.11. Speech. Economic Guideposts for Milk Merchandising (Box 23)
    - 1960. 35.12. Speech. Setting Our Sights for the Sixties--an Examination of Our Marketing Opportunities (Box 23)
    - 1960. 35.13. Speech. Marketing Opportunities in the Sixties (Box 23)
    - 1960. 36.1. Speech. Future of Retailing in the ‘60s--And What It Means to the Point-of-Purchase Producers (Box 23)
    - 1960. 36.2. Letter. To: Mr. William F. Wright, re: The economy 1960-1961 (Box 23)
    - 1960. 36.3. Speech. How Fabulous Will the 1960s Be? (Box 23)
    - 1960. 36.4. Speech. Food in the Sixties--Opportunity for Expansion of Rice Consumption (Box 23)
    - 1960. 36.5. Speech. Consumer Credit Potential in the ‘60s (Box 23)
    - 1960. 36.6. Speech. Marketing Opportunities in the Sixties (Box 23)
    - 1960. 36.7. Speech. Marketing Opportunities during the Next Decade (Box 23)
    - 1960. 36.8. Speech. Boom Ahead in World Trade with Rapid Advances in Living Standards (Box 23)
    - 1960. 36.9. Speech. World Trade and Travel Boom Ahead Sparked by Rapid Rise of Living Standards (Box 23)
    - 1960. 36.10. Client talk. United States Brewers Foundation. Rheingold meeting (Box 23)
    - 1960. 36.11. Speech. Marketing Opportunities in the Sixties (Box 23)
    - 1960. 36.12. Speech. Opportunities for Expansion in the Food Market in the Sixties (Box 23)
  - Johnson, Arno (continued), (81-87 of 112 folders) (Box 24)
    - 1960. 37.1. Client talk. Jos. Schlitz Brewing Company. Planning for the Future--Trends and Changes that May Affect Beer Potentials in the Next Decade (Box 24)
    - 1960. 37.2. Speech. Economic Guideposts for Milk Merchandising (Box 24)
    - 1960. 37.3. Speech. Role of Advertising Research in Expanding Our Economy (Box 24)
    - 1960. 37.4. Speech. Marketing Impact of Population Trends (Box 24)
    - 1960. 37.5. Letter. To: Mr. Meek, re: Monetary Policy--Its Relation to Inflation and Standard of Living (Box 24)
    - 1960. 37.6. Client talk. Reader’s Digest. Talk to sales & advertising executives based on Selling to Tomorrow's Consumer (Box 24)
    - 1960. 37.7. Speech. Selling to Tomorrow's Consumer (Box 24)
    - 1960. 37.8. Speech. JWT Board of Directors Meeting (Box 24)
    - 1960. 37.9. Speech. Selling Tomorrow's Consumer (Box 24)
    - 1961. 37.10. Letter. To: Mr. Tom O'Grady, re: Income and occupation as an influence on beer potential (Box 24)
    - 1961. 37.11. Speech. Selling Tomorrow's Consumer (Box 24)
    - 1961. 37.12. Client talk. Lever Brothers Company. Opportunities for Expansion in the Grocery Products Market in the 1960s (Box 24)
    - 1961. 38.1. Speech. Selling to Tomorrow's Consumer (Box 24)
    - 1961. 38.2. Letter. To: Mr. Samuel Meek, re: Advertising, a Dynamic Force in the Democratic Process (Box 24)
    - 1961. 38.3. Speech. Selling to Tomorrow's Consumer (Box 24)
    - 1961. 38.4. Speech. Citizen’s National Bank. Selling to Tomorrow's Consumer (Box 24)
    - 1961. 38.5. Speech. United States Economy--Present and Future (Box 24)
    - 1961. 38.6. Speech. Advertising--a Dynamic Factor in Economic Growth (Box 24)
    - 1961. 38.7. Speech. World Economy (Box 24)
    - 1961. 38.8. Client talk. Francis I. Du Pont. Selling to Tomorrow's Consumer (Box 24)
    - 1961. 38.9. Speech. Advertising--a Dynamic Force in Economic Growth (Box 24)
    - 1961. 38.10. Speech. Selling to Tomorrow's Retail Consumer (Box 24)
    - 1961. 38.11. Speech. Economic Guideposts for Milk Merchandising (Box 24)
    - 1961. 38.12. Client talk. Oscar Mayer. Selling to Tomorrow's Consumer (Box 24)
    - 1961. 38.13. Speech. Selling to Tomorrow's Consumer (Box 24)
    - 1961. 38.14. Article. U. S. Living Standard Can Rise 55% by 1971. Advertising Age, Market Data issue, May 8 (Box 24)
    - 1961. 38.15. Speech. Advertising--a Dynamic Force in Economic Growth (Box 24)
    - 1961. 39.1. Speech. Vigorous Business Recovery Ahead? (Box 24)
    - 1961. 39.2. Speech. Vigorous Business Recovery Ahead? (Box 24)
    - 1961. 39.3. Client talk. Mobile Homes Manufacturing Association. Business Recovery and Expansion of the Mobile Home Market (Box 24)
    - 1961. 39.4. Speech. Music Industry--Growth Opportunities and Marketing Challenges of the Next Decade (Box 24)
    - 1961. 39.5. Speech. Explosive Growth of World Markets Ahead (Box 24)
    - 1961. 39.6. Speech. Explosive Growth of World Markets Ahead (Box 24)
    - 1961. 39.7. Client talk. Hospital Saving Association of Chapel Hill. Economic Trends of Importance to Blue Cross & Blue Shield (Box 24)
    - 1961. 39.8. Speech. Changing Characteristics of the Population (Box 24)
    - 1961. 39.9. Speech. Expanding Needs of Consumers and the Expanding Potential for Consumer Credit (Box 24)
    - 1961. 39.10. Speech. Opportunities for Expansion in the Food Market (Box 24)
    - 1961. 39.11. Letter. To: Mr. S. W. Meek, re: Four fallacies relating to inflation (Box 24)
    - 1961. 40.1. Other writing. Explosive Growth of World Markets. Faye Henle (WOR) interview for Your Pocketbook radio program (Box 24)
    - 1961. 40.2. Speech. Changing Characteristics of the Population (Box 24)
    - 1961. 40.2a. Speech. Advertising--The Positive Force in Economic Growth and Better Living Standards (Box 24)
    - 1961. 40.3. Letter. To: Henry Flower, re: Life insurance premiums versus disposable income and personal saving (Box 24)
    - 1961. 40.4. Speech. Advertising--The Positive Force in Economic Growth and Better Living Standards (Box 24)
    - 1961. 40.5. Speech. Unwrapping the Future (Box 24)
    - 1961. 40.6. Client talk. Francis I. du Pont. Economic Changes Affecting Your Economy (Box 24)
    - 1961. 40.7. Speech. Economic Changes Affecting Your Market (Box 24)
    - 1961. 40.8. Speech. Vigorous Business Recovery Ahead? (Box 24)
    - 1961. 40.9. Speech. Vigorous Business Recovery Ahead? (Box 24)
  - Johnson, Arno (continued), (88-94 of 112 folders) (Box 25)
    - 1961. 40.10. Speech. Profit Opportunities in Selected Markets (Box 25)
    - 1961. 40.11. Speech. JWT Board of Directors Meeting (Box 25)
    - 1962. 40.12. Speech. Vigorous Business Recovery Ahead? (Box 25)
    - 1962. 40.13. Speech. Vigorous Business Recovery Ahead? (Box 25)
    - 1962. 40.14. Client talk. American Bankers Association. Some Economic Trends to Be Considered in Bank Advertising Plans (Box 25)
    - 1962. 40.15. Speech. Where Do We Stand? (Box 25)
    - 1962. 40.16. Client talk. National Fisheries Institute. Economic Trends Point to Growth in Market Potentials for Fish and Shell Fish (Box 25)
    - 1962. 41.1. Client talk. American Bankers Association. Some Economic Trends to Be Considered in Bank Advertising Plans (Box 25)
    - 1962. 41.2. Client talk. Pan American World Airways. The Potential in European Travel Is Tenfold Greater than Actually Realized (Box 25)
    - 1962. 41.3. Client talk. Ford Dealer Association. The 7½ Million Car Market (Box 25)
    - 1962. 41.4. Speech. Vigorous Business Growth Ahead (Box 25)
    - 1962. 41.5. Speech. Some Economic Trends to Be Considered in Financial Plans (Box 25)
    - 1962. 41.6. Speech. Where Do We Stand? (Box 25)
    - 1962. 41.7. Speech. Vigorous Business Growth Ahead--If We Sell (Box 25)
    - 1962. 41.8. Client talk. Radio Corporation of America. The Economic Outlook and its Advertising Implications (Box 25)
    - 1962. 41.9. Article. Vigorous Recovery and Price Stability Possible in 1962-63 if We Increase Advertising to Expand Consumption. Advertising Age, Market Data issue, May 14 (Box 25)
    - 1962. 41.10. Speech. Some Economic and Social Trends Affecting Recreation Planning--The Task to Achievement--Optimum Utilization of America's Facilities (Box 25)
    - 1962. 41.11. Speech. Speech before agency leaders from outside the U.S. (Box 25)
    - 1962. 41.12. Speech. Why Advertising Education Is Important (Box 25)
    - 1962. 41.13. Letter. To: Tom Sutton, re: Consumer markets by income groups (made by Harry Henry of Thomson Organization Ltd) (Box 25)
    - 1962. 41.14. Client talk. Radio Corporation of America. The Economic Outlook and its Advertising Implications (Box 25)
    - 1962. 41.15. Speech. Changing Characteristics of the Population (Box 25)
    - 1962. 41.16. Client talk. Francis I. du Pont. Vigorous Recovery and Price Stability Possible in 1962-63 (Box 25)
    - 1962. 41.17. Letter. To: Howard Brundage, re: Investment Committee meeting (current economic situation) (Box 25)
    - 1962. 41.18. Speech. Changing Characteristics of the Population (Box 25)
    - 1962. 41.19. Speech. Summary of Current Economic Situation (Box 25)
    - 1962. 42.1. Speech. Dynamic Trends in World Markets (Box 25)
    - 1962. 42.2. Other writing. Are We Shackling Economic Growth by Overlooking the Consumer? (booklet) (Box 25)
    - 1962. 42.2a. Letter. To: Harry A. Lee (JWT San Francisco), re: Booklet, questions by Mr. Vesper (Standard Oil) (Box 25)
    - 1962. 42.3. Article. Western Europe--a $12 Billion Advertising Potential by 1972. Media Agencies Clients, Sept. 10 (Box 25)
    - 1962. 42.4. Letter. To: Norman Strouse, re: Misleading interpretation that rise in ratio of advertising to sales implies a decrease in advertising effectiveness (Box 25)
    - 1962. 42.5. Speech. Economic Guideposts in Milk Merchandising (Box 25)
    - 1962. 42.6. Letter. To: 22 VPs (suggested by E.G.Wilson) for Board of Directors Meeting, re: Summary of current economic situation (Box 25)
    - 1962. 42.7. Article. Dynamic Growth in World Markets Ahead. International Trade Review, Nov. (Box 25)
    - 1962. 42.8. Other writing. Answers to questions (attached) submitted by S.W.Meek (Box 25)
    - 1962. 43.1. Speech. World Markets for Athletic Goods (given by John Van Zant) (Box 25)
    - 1962. 43.2. Speech. Changing American Community (Box 25)
    - 1962. 43.3. Speech. Changing American Community (Box 25)
    - 1962. 43.4. Speech. Impromptu talk to Advertising Club of The Hague (visitors) (Box 25)
    - 1962. 43.5. Client talk. Francis I. du Pont. Some Factors Pointing to Future Investment Growth (Box 25)
    - 1962. 43.6. Letter. Summary of Current Economic Situation (Box 25)
    - 1962. 43.7. Speech. Factors Affecting Our Business Growth in Coming Years; used as basis for article in The World of Advertising issue of Advertising Age, Jan. 15, page 286 (Box 25)
    - 1962. 43.8. Client talk. Scott Paper Company. Some Factors Pointing to Future Growth of the Market-For Food and Household Products (Box 25)
    - 1962. 43.9. Letter. Summary of Current Economic Situation (Box 25)
    - 1962. 43.10. Letter. Summary of Current Economic Situation (Box 25)
    - 1962. 43.11. Client talk. Need for Sales to Match Productive Ability (Box 25)
    - 1963. 43.11a. Speech. Rerun of AMA talk (Box 25)
    - 1963. 43.12. Speech. Some Factors Pointing to Future Shopping Center Growth (Box 25)
    - 1963. 43.13. Client talk. Pan American World Airways. Dynamic Growth in World Markets Ahead (Box 25)
    - 1963. 43.14. Speech. Review and Forecast Time (Box 25)
    - 1963. 43.15. Letter. Summary of Current Economic Situation (Box 25)
    - 1963. 43.16. Speech. Need for Sales to Match Productive Ability (Box 25)
    - 1963. 43.17. Speech. Changing American Community (Box 25)
    - 1963. 43.18. Speech. Researching Dynamic Market Trends that Will Affect Your Growth and Profits (Box 25)
  - Johnson, Arno (continued), (95-100 of 112 folders) (Box 26)
    - 1963. 43.19. Speech. Changing Economic Conditions Affecting Market Strategy (Box 26)
    - 1963. 43.20. New Business. Pacific Telephone & Telegraph. Changing Economic Conditions Affecting Market Strategy (Box 26)
    - 1963. 43.21. Speech. Are We Prepared to Unshackle Economic Growth? (Box 26)
    - 1963. 43.22. Client talk. National Fisheries Institute. Economic Patterns--Some Factors Pointing to Future Growth of the Market for Fish & Shell Fish (Box 26)
    - 1963. 44.1. Article. Are We Prepared to Unshackle Economic Growth? Advertising Age, Market Data issue, May 6 (Box 26)
    - 1963. 44.2. Speech. Economic and Social Trends Affecting Your Market Opportunities and Distribution (Box 26)
    - 1963. 44.3. Client talk. Quaker Oats Company. Economic and Social Trends Affecting Your Market Opportunities and Distribution (Box 26)
    - 1963. 44.4. Speech. World Agricultural Prosperity in 1968--And Beyond (Box 26)
    - 1963. 44.5. Speech. Increasing Economic Role of Advertising (Box 26)
    - 1963. 44.6. Speech. Need for Sales to Match Production Ability (Box 26)
    - 1963. 44.7. Speech. Stop Underestimating Your Sales Potentials (Box 26)
    - 1963. 44.8. Letter. To: Mr. S. W. Meek, re: Comments on U.S. Steel Corporation Annual Report (Box 26)
    - 1963. 44.9. Client talk. Scott Paper Company. Some Factors Pointing to Future Growth of the Market for Food and Household Products (Box 26)
    - 1963. 44.10. Other writing. Isn’t the Consumer the Real Key to Continued Economic Growth? (booklet) (Box 26)
    - 1963. 44.11. Speech. World-Wide Opportunity for Better Living Standards (Box 26)
    - 1963. 44.12. Letter. To: William L. Banks, re: Discretionary spending power (Box 26)
    - 1963. 44.13. Article. World-Wide Opportunity for Better Living Standards, AAAA reprint of Harvard talk (See #11) (Box 26)
    - 1963. 44.14. Client talk. Scott Paper Company. Some Factors Pointing to Future Growth of the Market for Food and Household Products (Box 26)
    - 1963. 45.1. Client talk. United States Brewers Association. Planning for the Future and Changes that May Affect Beer Potentials in the Next Decade (Box 26)
    - 1963. 45.2. Speech. Stop Underestimating Your Sales Potentials (Box 26)
    - 1963. 45.3. Speech. Changing Economic Conditions Affecting Market Strategy (Box 26)
    - 1963. 45.4. Speech. Population Studies: 5 Changing Characteristics of the Population that Will Affect Planning for the Super-City of Tomorrow (Faye Henle, WOR, interview on Super-City of Tomorrow) (Box 26)
    - 1963. 45.5. Speech. Isn't the Consumer the Real Key to Continued Economic Growth? (Box 26)
    - 1963. 45.6. Speech. Some Factors Pointing to Future Growth of the Market for Food, Household, and Personal Care Products (Box 26)
    - 1963. 45.7. Speech. Changing American Community (Box 26)
    - 1964. 46.1. Client talk. Scott Paper Company. Some Factors Pointing to Future Growth of the Market for Food, Household, and Personal Care Products (Box 26)
    - 1964. 46.2. Speech. Developing and Expanding Domestic Markets for Agricultural Products (Box 26)
    - 1964. 46.3. Client talk. United States Brewers Association. Planning for the Future--Trends and Changes that May Affect Beer Potentials in the Next Decade (Box 26)
    - 1964. 46.4. Speech. Stop Underestimating Your Sales Potentials (Box 26)
    - 1964. 46.5. Speech. Promise of 1974 (Box 26)
    - 1964. 46.6. Speech. Isn't the Consumer the Real Key to Continued Economic Growth? (Box 26)
    - 1964. 46.7. Speech. Economic and Social Trends Affecting Market Opportunities for Agricultural Products (Box 26)
    - 1964. 46.8. Client talk. 7 food clients. (Box 26)
    - 1964. 46.9. Speech. Our Economy and Opportunities for Growth (Box 26)
    - 1964. 46.10. Speech. Economic and Social Trends Affecting Market Opportunities for Agricultural Products (Box 26)
    - 1964. 46.11. Speech. Isn't the Consumer the Real Key to Continued Economic Growth? (Box 26)
    - 1964. 46.12. Speech. Marketing Profile--10 Factors that Can Mean More Sales (Box 26)
    - 1964. 46.13. Article. Need Ad Push; Consumer Sales Lag. Advertising Age, Market Data issue, May 4 (Box 26)
    - 1964. 46.14. Speech. U.S. Market-Picture of Dynamic Changes & Expanding Potentials (Box 26)
    - 1964. 46.15. Speech. Tomorrow's Tomorrow (Box 26)
  - Johnson, Arno (continued), (101-106 of 112 folders) (Box 27)
    - 1964. 47.1. Speech. Areas of Opportunities in Projections (Box 27)
    - 1964. 47.2. Speech. U.S.Market--Picture of Dynamic Changes (Box 27)
    - 1964. 47.3. Speech. Changing American Community (Box 27)
    - 1964. 47.4. Speech. Background of Planning and Progress (Box 27)
    - 1964. 47.5. Speech. Changing American Community--Its Impact on Public Relations in the South (Box 27)
    - 1964. 47.6. Speech. Challenge of Our Times (Box 27)
    - 1964. 47.7. Speech. Decade of Opportunity--1964 to 1974 (Box 27)
    - 1964. 47.8. Speech. Sixties Still Got a Lot to Give--Newspapers (Box 27)
    - 1964. 47.9. Speech. Improvement in Consumer Standard of Living Key to Free World Economic Growth (Box 27)
    - 1964. 47.10. Speech. Decade of Opportunity--To 1974 (Box 27)
    - 1964. 47.11. Speech. Decade of Opportunity--1965 to 1975 (Box 27)
    - 1964. 48.1. Discussion. Advertising Mix--Teamwork for Plus Sales (Box 27)
    - 1964. 48.2. Article. Look Forward--Not Backward. Advertising Age, Centennial Issue, Dec. 7 (Box 27)
    - 1965. 48.3. Speech. Decade of Opportunity--1965 to 1975 (Box 27)
    - 1965. 48.4. Speech. American Economy's Impact on the Bike Boom (Box 27)
    - 1965. 48.5. Article. Discretionary Spending Power and Consumer Credit. Advertising Age, Mar. 1; American Banker, Mar. 16; Journal Commerce, June 1 (Box 27)
    - 1965. 48.6. Speech. Growth of the Economy--1965 to 1975 (Box 27)
    - 1965. 48.7. Speech. Decade of Opportunity--1965 to 1975 (Box 27)
    - 1965. 48.8. Article. Inadequate Growth of Advertising Threatens Our Future. Advertising Age, May 24 (Box 27)
    - 1965. 48.9. Speech. Decade of Opportunity--1965 to 1975 (Box 27)
    - 1965. 48.10. Speech. Decade of Opportunity--1965 to 1975 (Box 27)
    - 1965. 48.11. Speech. Decade of Opportunity--1965 to 1975 (Box 27)
    - 1965. 48.12. Client talk. Institute of Life Insurance. The U. S. Economy in the Next Decade (Box 27)
    - 1965. 48.13. Speech. Decade of Opportunity Worldwide--1965 to 1975 (Box 27)
    - 1965. 48.14. Speech. Decade of Opportunity--1965 to 1975 (Box 27)
    - 1965. 48.15. Speech. Decade of Opportunity--1965 to 1975 (Box 27)
    - 1965. 48.16. Article. Annual Food Sales of $125 Billion Possible in 10 Years--by 1975. Food Business, Sept. (Box 27)
    - 1965. 49.1. Speech. Golden Decade for Floor Covering 1966-1975 (Box 27)
    - 1965. 49.2. Speech. Decade of Opportunity Worldwide--1965-1975 (Box 27)
    - 1965. 49.3. Speech. Framework of American Markets in 1975 (Box 27)
    - 1965. 49.4. Client talk. Burry Biscuit. The Decade of Opportunity Worldwide--1965 to 1975, plus Cookie tables (Box 27)
    - 1965. 49.5. New Business. Armour & Company. The Decade of Opportunity Worldwide--1965 to 1975, plus Meat and Fish tables (Box 27)
    - 1966. 49.6. Speech. Decade of Opportunity for Marketing--1966 to 1975 (Box 27)
    - 1966. 49.7. Speech. Decade of Opportunity for Marketing--1966 to 1975 (Box 27)
    - 1966. 49.8. Speech. Decade of Opportunity 1966 to 1975...Newspapers (Box 27)
    - 1966. 49.9. Speech. Advertising's Biggest Job--Jobs (Box 27)
    - 1966. 49.10. Speech. Role of Advertising in Economic Growth (Box 27)
    - 1966. 49.11. Speech. Economist's View of the Food Service Industry (Box 27)
    - 1966. 49.12. Speech. Marketing's Biggest Job--Jobs (Box 27)
    - 1966. 49.13. Article. Advertising's Biggest Job--Jobs. Advertising Age, Market Data issue, Apr. 25 (Box 27)
    - 1966. 49.14. Speech. Decade of Opportunity for Marketing 1966 to 1976 (Box 27)
    - 1966. 49.15. Speech. Decade of Opportunity--1966 to 1976 (Box 27)
  - Johnson, Arno (continued), (107-112 of 112 folders) (Box 28)
    - 1966. 50.1. Speech. Decade of Change--1966 to 1976 (Box 28)